{
    "id": "ee4ae3e7cae04e86bcf8928d38a0b7ac",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He met his future wife ……………………… a party.",
            "description": "We use at in the expressions at a party, at the cinema, at the theatre, at university etc.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "689f20f755a14787897bcc69e3f15bdb"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were friends ………………………. university.",
            "description": "We use at in the expressions at a party, at the cinema, at the theatre, at university etc.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a18bb903458b4b0b8cefc9fd24ffc083"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s take our time and go …………………. boat.",
            "description": "We use by in expressions like by car, by bus, by bike, by boat, by plane etc.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ca78732f847a489e84ba5f5f8d990422"
        },
        {
            "question": "She goes to school ……………………….. foot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c09987a452ab487c8d4b54653907e1ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "She decided to quit her job ………………………. several reasons.",
            "description": "We use for with reason.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bf2c3c064329478e852fa192f817825f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never see things ………………………… my point of view.",
            "description": "We use from with point of view.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "according to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9910fd078a2647a187b59e380fd9faad"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. my opinion, she shouldn’t have married him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "On",
                "According to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "75184710c9ec451a856bb005deae7d88"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… the end, I have found a good job.",
            "description": "In the end means finally.",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "At",
                "On"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21493ffeaebf48bbb41e9aeaa4f406af"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am paid ……………………….. the end of the month.",
            "description": "At the end means at the point where something ends.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cab7ed40c1d74d01be604a6b1a8b1afb"
        },
        {
            "question": "You look quite pretty …………………………. this photo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "601913b9b91b45489e90c340a24bed06"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting started ……………………. time.",
            "description": "On time means at the planned time.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d71665054126405caa5cd916edfd65f1"
        }
    ]
}